A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Office of the Arts, Program Files FA640
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Files, 1955-1977; XIII
  - Museum Curatorial Training Program -- Nominator Lists, 1964-1972 (Box 55)
  - Museum Curatorial Training Program -- Order of Discussion, 1964-1972 (Box 55)
  - Museum Curatorial Training Program -- Nominees, 1965-1972 (Box 55)
  - Monographs Program -- Background, 1961-1964 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Editorial Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Yale University Press, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Gordon, Irene, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Grant Actions and Appropriations, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Judges Correspondence, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Monographs Program -- Judges Meeting, Jan 5, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Background, 1960-1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Companies Interested in Participating, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Forms, 1960-1961 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Grant Actions, 1961-1965 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Nominees' Correspondence, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Judges Correspondence, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Judges Meeting, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Nominators' Correspondence, 1961 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Press Releases, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Statistics, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- General, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Baltimore Civic Opera, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Boston, Opera Company of, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Central City Opera House Association, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Chautauqua Opera Association, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Cincinnati Summer Opera, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Connecticut Opera Association, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Fort Worth Opera Association, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Goldovsky Opera Theater, 1963-1966 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Houston Grant Opera Association Inc, 1962-1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Kansas City Lyric Theatre, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Miami, Opera Guild of Greater, 1962-1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- New Orleans Opera House Association Inc, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Opera Association of New Mexico, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Philadelphia Lyric Opera Company Inc, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Pittsburgh Opera Inc, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- (San Antonio) Symphonic Society, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Santa Fe Opera, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Spring Opera of San Francisco, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Opera Singers Program -- Participating Organizations -- Washington, Opera Society of, 1962-1964 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Background and Planning, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Candidates, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Forms, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grant Actions, 1968 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Judges Meeting, Jul 19-20, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Judges' Correspondence, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Nominators, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Nominees, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Participating Theaters, 1963-1967 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Clemons, Walter, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Eastlake, William, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Elliott, George P., 1963 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Foote, Shelby, 1963-1967 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Goyen, William, 1963-1973 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Hawkes, John, 1963-1966 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Justic, Donald, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Marshall, Paule, 1963-1973 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Merwin, W.S., 1964 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Powers, J.F., 1964-1966 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Roth, Philip, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Sexton, Anne, 1963-1969 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Smith, William Jay, 1964-1966 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Swenson, May, 1964-1965 (Box 56)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers Program -- Grantees -- Wagoner, David, 1964-1965 (Box 56)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Scripts Announced in Awards Release, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominating Forms, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Agreement Letters, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Letters to Nominators, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- List of Nominators, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Synopses and Evaluations of Scripts Recommended to Judges, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Background, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Actors Workshop, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Alley Theatre, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Stage Arena, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Art Institute of Chicago, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence -- Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Forms, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grant Actions, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Judges Correspondence, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Judges Meeting, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- New Dramatists Committee, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominators' Correspondence, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Adams, James, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Blum, Edwin Harvey, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Background, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Forms, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grant Actions, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Judges Correspondence, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Judges Declinations, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Judges Meeting, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- New Dramatists Committee, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominators Correspondence, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominees, A-G, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominees, H-N, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Nominees, O-Z, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Statistics, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Payment Records, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Press Releases, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Readers, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Scripts Not Recommended, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Scripts Recommended, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Charles Best, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Josh Greenfeld, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- John Briard Harding, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Sidney Michaels, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Philip Pruneau, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Syril Schochen, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- John Vlahos, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees -- Lionel Wiggam, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Actor's Workshop, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Alley Theatre, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Arena Stage, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Boston University Theatre, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Carnegie Institute Department of Drama, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Margo Jones Theatre, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Playhouse, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Omaha Community Playhouse, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Stanford Memorial Theatre, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Participating Theaters -- Tulsa Little Theatre, 1958 (Box 58)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- Letters to Nominators, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- Nominating Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- Biographical Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- List of Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- List of Participating Organizations, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- Financial Schedule, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Poets and Fiction Writers, Program for -- Material from Juror's Meeting, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Directors in the Professional Theater, Program for -- Letters to Nominators, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Directors in the Professional Theater, Program for -- Nominating Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Directors in the Professional Theater, Program for -- List of Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Directors in the Professional Theater, Program for -- Biographical Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Directors in the Professional Theater, Program for -- Financial Schedule, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Letters to Nominators, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominating Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Letters to Nominated Artists, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Memorandum to Participating Artists -- Page 1's; Page 2's for regions 1-4, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Memorandum to Participating Artists -- Page 2's for regions 5-9, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Memorandum to Finalists, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Letter to Unsuccessful Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Confidential Inquiry Form, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Financial Schedule, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- List of Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- List of Finalists, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Summary Compiled for National Jury of Entries Submitted by Finalists, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Instructions to National Jury, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Condition Reports; Pickup Requests; Shipping Instructions, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Miscellaneous Material (carbon copies), 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Letters to Nominators, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Nominating Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Letter to Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- List of Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Biographical Forms, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Summary of Personnel Listed in Statements Submitted, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Theater Design, Program for -- Letter to Unsuccessful Nominees, 1959 (Box 60)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Publishers A-Z (1/2), 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Publishers A-Z (2/2), 1970-1971 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Summary Information, [1972-1973] (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Publishers Narrative Reports, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Composers A-Z, 1971 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Composer's Control Sheets, 1975 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Publisher's Control Sheets, 1975 (Box 61)
  - Recording-Publication Program -- Richard P. Kapp Memoranda, 1969-1971 (Box 61)
  - Strengthening Institutional Resources in Humanities and Arts -- Background, 1967-1968 (Box 62)
  - Strengthening Institutional Resources in Humanities and Arts -- Grant Actions, 1967-1970 (Box 62)
  - Strengthening Institutional Resources in Humanities and Arts -- Grant Actions, 1968-1970 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Comments, 1965-1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Consultants, 1964-1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- ASOL Incoming Letters, 1964-1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Evaluations, 1972 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Forms, 1965-1975 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Grant Actions and Appropriations, 1966-1972 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- List of Majors, Metropolitans and New Metropolitans -- Grants and Recommendations, 1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background, 1964-Oct 24, 1965 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background, Oct 22, 1965-May 1, 1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background, May 1, 1966-1971 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background, 1972-1974 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background/Trust Agreement -- Memoranda, Reports, Press Releases, Bank Agreements (1/2), 1964-1972 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background/Trust Agreement -- Memoranda, Reports, Press Releases, Bank Agreements (2/2), 1964-1972 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background -- Press Releases, 1965-1973 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background -- Letter of Grant/Terms of Grant, 1966 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Background -- Worksheets, 1965 (Box 62)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Discussions with Orchestras, 1965 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Dockets and Discussion Papers (1/2), 1965 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Dockets and Discussion Papers (2/2), 1965 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Dockets and Discussion Papers / Trustees Meeting, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Docket Drafts, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Docket, 1966 (Box 63)
  - Symphony Orchestra Program -- Annual Report Forms, 1966-1975 (Box 63)
  - Translations Program -- Background, 1962-1964 (Box 63)
  - Translations Program -- Correspondence and Interview Diaries, 1962-1963 (Box 63)
  - Translations Program -- Grant Actions and Appropriations, 1964-1972 (Box 63)
  - Independent Schools of Art (A-Z), 1963-1969 (Box 63)
  - Scenic Design, 1961 (Box 63)
  - Writers, Poets and Fiction -- Nominations and Statements of Purpose, 1959 (Box 64)
    See also Ford Foundation Project file C-918: Grants in Aid program for novelists and poets, and Grant files: 06000132 (PA60-132), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), PROGRAM FOR POETS AND FICTION WRITERS; 06090149 (PA60-149), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), COOPERATION OF THEATERS AND OPERA COMPANIES IN PROGRAM FOR POETS AND FICTION WRITERS; 06000513 (PA63-513), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), PROGRAM FOR POETS AND FICTION WRITERS; 06390514 (PA63-514), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), COOPERATION OF THEATERS AND OPERA COMPANIES IN PROGRAM FOR POETS AND FICTION WRITERS.
  - Writers, Poets and Fiction, 1963 (Box 64)
  - Writers, Poets and Fiction -- Grantees, 1963 (Box 64)
    1959 Grantees include: George Garrett – Alley Theatre, Houston; Herbert Gold – Actor’s Workshop, San Francisco; Mark Harris – Actor’s Workshop, San Francisco; Anthony Hecht – Actors’ Studio and Phoenix Theatre, New York; Robert Lowell – New York City Opera Company and Metropolitan Opera Association; William Meredith – New York City Opera Company and Metropolitan Opera Association; James Purdy – Actors’ Studio, New York; James Schevill – Theatre Workshop, Theatre Royal, London; Eudora Welty – Actors’ Studio and Phoenix Theatre, New York.
    1963 Grantees include: Walter Clemons - Alley Theatre; William Eastlake - Actor's Workshop; Shelby Foote - Arena Stage; William Goyen - Lincoln Center Repertory Theatre and American Shakespeare Festival; William S. Merwin - Royal Shakespeare Theatre, Aldwych Theartre.
  - Directors, Program for -- Nominations and Statements of Purpose, 1958 (Box 64)
  - Directors, Program for -- Grantees, 1958 (Box 64)
  - Directors, Program for -- Nominations and Statements of Purpose, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Directors, Program for -- Grantees, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Creative Writers -- Grantees, 1958 (Box 64)
    Grantees include: James Baldwin, Saul Bellow, E.E. Cummings, Robert Fitzgerald, Stanley J. Kunitz, Bernard Malmud, Flannery O’Connor, Tillie Olsen, Katherine Anne Porter, Theodore H. Roethke, and Niccolo Tucci.
  - Creative Writers -- Nominations, 1958 (Box 64)
  - Design, Theater -- Grantees, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Design, Theater -- Nominations and Statements of Purpose, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Reporters, Editors and Critics, Program for -- List of Applicants, 1964 (Box 64)
    Former file ID
    E-12: Program for Critics, Reviewers, and Editors in the Performing and Visual Arts.
  - Reporters, Editors and Critics, Program for -- Grantees, 1963-1964 (Box 64)
  - Reporters, Editors and Critics, Program for -- Grantees (1/2), 1964-1965 (Box 64)
  - Reporters, Editors and Critics, Program for -- Grantees (2/2), 1964-1965 (Box 64)
  - Studies in the Creative Arts -- Grantees, 1959-1962 (Box 64)
    See also Ford Foundation Project file D-22: Fellowship program for non-academic scholars in the creative arts (Studies in the Creative Arts); and Grant file 06090249 (PA60-249), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), “PROGRAM FOR STUDIES INTHE CREATIVE ARTS”.
  - Studies in the Creative Arts -- Lists of Applicants, 1959-1963 (Box 64)
  - Studies in the Creative Arts -- List of Applicants, 1962 (Box 64)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Grantees, 1961-1962 (Box 64)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Ford Foundation Press Release, Selection Committe Information, List of Nominees, 1961-1962 (Box 64)
  - Visual Artists Program -- Grantees, 1958 (Box 64)
  - Visual Artists Program -- Summary, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Summary, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Playwrights, Program for -- Grantees, 1958-1959 (Box 64)
  - Film makers Program -- Grantees -- Original Statements and Nominations (1/2), 1963 (Box 64)
    Also includes nominations for Helen Levitt and Kent Mackenzie from the photographer/film-maker Robert Frank.
    E-11: Program for Film Makers
  - Film makers Program -- Grantees -- Original Statements and Nominations (2/2), 1963 (Box 64)
    E-11: Program for Film Makers.
- Visual Arts Grants, 1958-1959; XIV
  1958 Grantees include: Grantees include: Josef Albers, Elmer Bishoff, Hyman Bloom, Edwin Dickinson, Philip Guston, Raoul Hague, Conrad Marca-Relli, Reuben Nakian, Theodore Roszak, Adja Yunkers.
  1959 Grantees include: Cosmo Campoli, Andrew Dasburg, Leon Golub, Gabriel Kohn, Loren MacIver, Hilda Morris, Kenzo Okada, Gabor Peterdi, Richard Pousette-Dart, and Bernard Reder.
  Purchase prizes awarded in connection with 1959 program: J. Bardin, Dorothy Berge, George Bireline, Byron Burford, David F. Driesbach, Jacob Elshin, Herbert L. Fink, Robert F. Gates, Leon Goldin, Roy Gussow, John Heliker, Paul Horiuchi, William Ivey, Max Kahn, Keith M. Martin, Carl Morris, Malcolm Myers, Richard Sussman, Joyce Treiman, Charles Umlauf, and John von Wicht.
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Participating Organization -- Region 1 -- American Federation of Arts, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 2 -- Institute of Contemporary Art, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 3 -- Carnegie Institute Department of Fine Arts, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 4 -- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 5 -- John and Mabel Ringling Museum of Art, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 6 -- Detroit Institute of Arts, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 7 -- Walker Art Center, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 8 -- University of Nebraska Art Galleries, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 9 -- Fort Worth Art Center, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 10 -- Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 11 -- California Palace of Legion of Honor, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Region 12 -- Seattle Art Museum, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Albers, Josef, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Bischoff, Elmer, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Bloom, Hyman, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Dickinson, Edwin, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Guston, Philip, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Hague, Raoul, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Marca-Relli, Conrad, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Nakian, Reuben, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Roszak, Theodore, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Yunkers, Adja, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- General -- Program Papers, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- General -- Materials Compiled for Meetings with National Jury, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- General -- Letters of Endorsement, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- General -- Correspondence and Comments, 1958-1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- General, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Lists and Letters, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Campoli, Cosmo, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Dasburg, Andrew, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Golub, Leon, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Kohn, Gabriel, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Maciver, Loren, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Morris, Hilda, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Okada, Kenzo, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Peterdi, Gabor, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Pousette-Dart, Richard, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Reder, Bernard, 1959 (Box 65)